cashunclaimed.com 2017-12-13

# Unclaimed Money - Cash Unclaimed Privacy Policy

PLEASE READ CAREFULLY USE OF THIS SITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK AND SUBJECT TO THE FOLLOWING: 

By using this website you are agreeing to the following privacy policy and are legally bound by them. 

Please read before accessing or using any content from this site. If you do not agree with any of the stated terms and conditions listed, then do not continue to access or use this site. By continueing to use this site you are signifying your acceptance of these terms and conditions. CashUnclaimed.com reserves the right to modify, add or remove any or all content at any time without prior notice or warning. 

Cash Unclaimed Money Search is committed to your privacy. The following statements disclose our information gathering and dissemination practices. We respect your privacy. This is why we have taken the time to disclose our information collection practices and our privacy policy. Please take the time to review this document. 

Of the information we do collect, we allow our visitors the following access to the information. 

The website does collect data that can identify its visitors. 

We collect information for the following purpose(s): 

* Research and development.  
* Building records of visitors without linking identifying information to the records for the purpose of research, analysis and reporting.  
* Assisting you in your search for unclaimed money  
* Signing you up for your membership, newsletter lists and related payment transactions  
* Sending sales and marketing materials to you for various products &/or services.

Use Of Email Addresses: 

If you provide us with your email address we will utilize it to send you email regarding our services and promotional messages. You can opt-out of these email messages at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of these emails. 

Who has access to the information we collect? 

Ourselves and/or our agents, partners & affiliates which utilize the information only for the purpose given. Information will only be shared with companies who also follow our privacy policies. 

How long is information kept? 

Information is retained for an indeterminate period of time. 

If you believe that our website has collected incorrect information or if you would like to dispute any information, please contact us using the address on this page. 

Cash Unclaimed Money Search does use cookies. 

On some payment processes (for example: if you choose to pay via paypal) our servers do not handle sensitive financial information such as credit card numbers. All financial transaction details are handled on the secure servers of PayPal.com. You can visit PayPal to read their privacy policy. 

This website may contain advertising from 3rd parties. These 3rd parties may have different privacy terms than Cashunclaimed maintains. You should check the privacy policies of those 3rd parties directly to understand those terms. 

Choice/Opt-out

Our Anti-Spam Policy tolerates only permission-based email. You may choose to opt-out of receiving email from us by submitting a request to opt out on our [customer support page](http://www.cashunclaimed.com/faq/). You always have the opportunity to opt-out or change preferences by following a link in the footer of all non-transactional email messages sent by us. In addition, any affiliate promoting CashUnclaimed.com is required to adhere to our strict no-Spam rules and are also required to allow you to opt out of their email marketing in a similar fashion. If you believe that you have received an unsolicited commercial email from us or any of our promotional affiliates, you may report it to us at our [customer support page](http://www.cashunclaimed.com/faq/). 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement and/or our practices involving your privacy, feel free to contact us at: 

CONTACT ADDRESS: 

CashUnclaimed.com  
19881 Brookhurst Street  
Suite C-285  
Huntington Beach, CA 92646  
br>
